<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Water Redefined]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Water Redefined]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/h2opulence/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 21:06:55 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/h2opulence/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WHAT IS PHYSICAL HEALTH?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>WHAT IS PHYSICAL HEALTH?</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/h2opulence/what-is-physical-health/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b623a35a-def2-4c86-b1a2-535919c130ae</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 21:06:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[ ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1></h1><p>Financial health is defined as one’s personal financial situation. There are many dimensions to financial health. Financial health is one of the greatest problems and challenges in the world. The rapidly evolving debt situation continues to skyrocket and many people can never seem to get out of a deep hole. Everything from personal debt, student loan debt, and credit card debt makes it hard for students and adults alike to get ahead. When one’s financial health is unstable this can cause sickness, stress, suffering, and poor decisions.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/h2opulence/financial-health/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">d77b4d6d-1e42-4c80-847a-e4f1a1d88521</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 21:06:13 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mind Your Mind]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Mind Your Mind</h1><p>Mental health refers to your mental state of mind and how it’s been fed through personal development, positive self talk, influential mentors, listening, speaking, learning and coaching. It’s been proven time and time again, that our minds hold the greatest power over our bodies, meaning the way we feel, our attitudes, our perception, and the way we view the world at large. Focusing on mental health is key because it’s so important to not only do physical exercises for our body, but also “push-ups” for the brain. We can never stop learning skills such as, relationship building, confidence, communication, public speaking, leadership, and mentorship. Making an investment into mental health is one of the greatest gifts to take your business and personal life to the next level!Always be sure to “mind” your mind.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/h2opulence/mind-your-mind/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">8b09eb14-2f63-4b91-840c-c4a09f5fa052</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2016 19:48:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>